威尔 · 森塔斯: 但问题是。
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: But here's the question.
我不仅仅是从 Twitter 上得到数据而不使用它。
I didn't just get that data
from Twitter to not use it.
我让它使用它，展示它，不管它可能是什么。
I got it to use it, display it,
whatever it might be.
但我不知道那些数据什么时候能回来。
But I don't know when that
data's gonna come back.
它随时都可能回来。
It could come back any time.
所以当数据回来的时候我需要 JavaScript
So I'm gonna need JavaScript to somehow
when the data does come back and
存储在一个属性中，自动运行一些代码来使用它。
get stored in a property, automatically
run some code on it to use it.
但我要怎么做呢？
But how am I gonna do that?
人们发现这个空数组
It turns out people that this empty array
在自己的履行财产也是非常重要的。
in the own fulfilled property
is also super damn important.
这个空数组将会有，或者我们可以放在这里，任何函数，任何代码,
This empty array is gonna have, or we can
put in there, any functions, any code,
我们希望在 JavaScript be 的帮助下自动生成
that we want to have automatically
with the help of JavaScript be
值属性填充时触发运行。
triggered to run when the value
property gets filled in.
当数据从 Twitter 上传回来的时候,
Which happens when the data
comes back from Twitter,
无论什么时候都会发生。
which happens whenever it does.
它会自动触发，在那一刻，数据
And it's going to automatically trigger,
at that moment, the data
从 Twitter 返回，自动获得 value 属性的更新。
comes back from Twitter, gets updated
on the value property, automatically.
它会自动触发存储在这个数组中的任何功能。
It's gonna automatically trigger any
functionality stored in this array.
因为在 JavaScript 中，你可以把函数存储在一个列表中。
Cuz in JavaScript,
you can store functions as in a list.
通常你可以在这里存储一个函数数组,
And usually into it you can store
an array of functions here,
我们可以加入一个函数。
we can put in a function.
我们在这个数组中插入的任何函数都会被自动触发运行
And any function we stick in this array
will be automatically triggered to run
当 value 属性更新时。
when the value property gets updated.
等待时机,
And wait for it,
值属性中的数据将自动插入作为输入,
that data in the value property
will be auto inserted as the input,
作为参数来填充任何存储在这里的函数的参数。
as the argument to fill in the parameter
of any function that's stored in here.
看看这个显示功能，得到了一个小参数，他们的数据。
So take a look at that display function
there, got a little parameter their data.
如果我们可以把显示存储在数组中,
If we could just get display
to be stored in that array,
它会自动运行，我们的数据会回来填补,
it would be automatically run and
our data that came back would fill in,
数据参数时，它是自动运行时显示为自动运行。
that data parameter when it's auto
run when display as auto run.
但是我们怎样才能把显示信息加入到数组中呢？
But how would we get
display into that array?
我如何通常实际洋红匹配这个地图？
How do I typically actually
magenta to match on this map?
我通常如何添加到什么方法？
How would I typically add to what method?
我必须加两个数组吗？
Do I have to add two arrays?
讲者2: 推 威尔 · 森特斯: 推。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: Push.
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Push.
它在未完成的属性上。
It's on the unfulfilled properties.
你只是在想我通常会怎么做。
You just sort of think
what would I do typically.
未来数据，点。
Future data, dot.
演讲者2: 点，未完成，点，推。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: Dot, unfulfilled, dot, push.
将句子: 点，推，然后通过显示功能。
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Dot, push and
then pass in the display function.
不幸的是，我们不能这样做，但是从根本上来说，是的，完全正确。
We can't do that unfortunately but
it's fundamentally, yeah, exactly right.
我们不能这么做。
We can't do that.
有没有人从我之前说的看出为什么我们不能这么做？
Did anyone spot why we can't do
that from what I said earlier?
汤姆 演讲者2: 这是一个隐藏的属性。
Tom?
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: It's a hidden property.
威尔 · 森坦斯: 隐藏财产。
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Hidden property.
隐藏的财产，甚至无法访问这个。
Hidden property,
can't even get access to this.
完全正确从 Tolls Pom。
Exactly right from Tolls Pom.
但是不要惊慌。
Don't panic though.
给了我们一个内置的方法，允许我们传递任何东西
JavaScript gives us a method built
in that allows us whatever we pass
它作为输入是否会被捕获并卡在数组中。
to whether it as input will be grabbed and
stuck in that array.
顺便问一下，在幕后，他们在做什么
By the way, behind the scenes,
what are they doing for
这些数据来抵消这个推动？
the data to unfulfill that push?
人们能发现什么可能是隐藏的，而不是隐藏的。
And what can people spot might
be that hidden, not that hidden.
你能发现什么，可能是把一个函数插入其中的方法
What can you spot might be that method
that sticks a function into that
未完成的任务，彼得？
unfulfilled array, Peter?
讲者2: 然后。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: Then.
威尔 · 森特斯: 没错，那么方法，那么点方法，没错，而且
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Exactly, the Then
method, the dot Then method, exactly, and
这就是我们将要看到的。
that's what we're going to see.
顺便说一下，我们稍后也会看到,
By the way, we're also going
to see in a moment later on,
我们稍后会讲到，这种方法是从哪里来的？
we're gonna see a little bit later on,
where's that method come from?
- 因为它不在这里-它不在这个物体上？
Because it ain't on here.
It isn't on this object?
我们来看看这么长时间以来,
We'll see, for
once we're in a session that so long,
今天下午我们要看看这个方法到底是从哪里来的。
we're gonna see where that method
actually comes from this afternoon.
好了。
There we go.
但是现在，让我们确切地做这一行。
But for now,
let's exactly do that line there.
我们来看看这里有什么东西能起作用。
Let's get something that's
going to function in here.
因为没有必要把数据从 Twitter 上带回来只是为了
Because there's no point bringing
data back from Twitter only for
消失在价值属性中。
it to disappear in the value property.
我们不知道会出现什么，所以我们不能直接使用它。
And we've no idea what's going to
show up so we can't use it directly.
我们必须确保我们有一个函数存储在这里。
We've got to make sure we have
a function stored in here.
它将由 JavaScript 自动运行。
It's going to be auto run
by JavaScript for us.
我们开始吧,
So here we go,
那就未来数据点吧
future data dot then
传递整个显示函数定义。
passing the entire display
function definition.
未来数据就是这个对象。
Okay, so future data is this object here.
它有一个未完成的属性。
It has an unfulfilled property.
我不会把所有的财产名称，我们已经得到了未履行的财产和
I'm not gonna put all the property names
and we've got the unfulfilled property and
不管传递到哪里，都会被拿走，对不起。
whatever gets passed to then,
it's just going to be nabbed, sorry.
在美国有这个词吗？
Is that a word in America?
是的。演讲者2: 是的。
It is.
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: Yes.
威尔 · 森塔斯: 英语中像19世纪棉花一样的单词将会被采用。
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: British word like a 19th
century cottony word is going to be taken.
只要有解析器，就会有解析器卡在里面。
Whenever it's parser there's gonna
be taken and stuck in there.
这正是我们所做的。
And that's exactly what we do.
我们使用 display 函数，然后使用未实现的数组。
We take the display function and
stuck into the unfulfilled array.
我们把它放进去。
Let's put it in.
这就是我们在未实现的数组中的显示功能。
There it is, our display function
in the unfulfilled array.
看看，多漂亮啊？
Look at that, isn't that beautiful?
我的天啊。
My goodness.
啊哈,
[LAUGH]
Aha,
这些都是通过这两条线实现的。
that was all achieved by those two lines.
但是这位女神已经准备好了吗？
But has this goddess all set up?
当然了。
You bet it has.
我们现在有了所有的设备。
We have all our setup now.
我们在背景中对着互联网说话。
We're speaking to the Internet
in the background.
我们有一个很好的连接到一个很好的对象在这里回到 JavaScript。
We've got a nice connection to a nice
object here back in JavaScript.
当时间来自网络的时候，我们的价值就会被填满
It's gonna be filled in with our value
when the time comes from the network
请求响应。
request responses.
凯拉说，旧的满足数组现在有一个功能，将
Kayla said, the old fulfilled
array now has a function that will
当数据返回时自动运行。
automatically run when
that data comes back.
我们结束了。
We're done.
我们继续大概，比如说一毫秒。
We get to plow on to at roughly,
let's say one millisecond.
到哪一行。
What line over to.
伊森，我们一毫秒到达哪条线？
Ethan, what line do we
hit at one millisecond?
演讲者2: 控制台日志，我先来。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: Console log, me first.
威尔 · 森特斯: 太棒了，我喜欢每个人都这样。
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Fantastic,
I love everybody staying so.
精确地聚焦，控制台日志(“我第一”) ,
Focus as well exactly,
console log('Me first'),
就在控制台里。
there it is in a console.
我们有，我先来。
And we have, Me first.
这里是1毫秒。
There it is at 1 millisecond.
威尔 · 森特斯: 我对这件事感到遗憾的是，这里的这一点是这样的
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: The one thing I regret
on this is this bit here being so
接近狂躁的创造物的权利。
close to the manic creation to the right.
让我们稍微移动一下。
So let's move this slightly.
意识到准备就绪---- 那是半程马拉松的长度，对吗？
Sense of readiness,
that's how long a half marathon is, right?
威尔 · 森塔斯: 3英里，3英里。
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: 3 miles, 3 miles.
我姐姐三月份要参加全程马拉松，亲爱的，随便啦。
My sister's doing a full marathon
in March, dear, whatever.
非常为她骄傲，非常骄傲，非常骄傲。
Very proud of her, very proud, very proud.
那么我们用的是哪一个呢？
So which one are we using here?
我们正在使用网络请求功能，不是吗？
We're using the network request feature,
weren't we?
大家听好了，标签是什么？
What was the label, everybody?
说话人3: 取回 威尔 · 森特斯: 拿回来，没错，是的,
&gt;&gt; Speaker 3: Fetch.
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Fetch, exactly, yeah,
取。
fetch.
这是我们使用网络请求的 JavaScript 标签
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: That's our JavaScript
label for using the network request for
彼此。
each other.
但这是双管齐下的，所以
But it's a two-pronged, so
在 JavaScript 中也有类似的结果---- 相当惊人。
it also has consequences in
JavaScript as well, pretty amazing.
好吧，当我这么做的时候，你不会相信发生了什么。
Okay, so while I was doing that,
you won't believe what happened.
成功地把我们送回到，比如说，我们应该说什么,
Twitter successfully sends us back at,
let's say, what should we say,
大概270毫秒吧？
like 270 milliseconds,
something like that?
是的，270毫秒。
Yeah, 270 milliseconds.
在270毫秒时，我们得到了好消息。
At 270 milliseconds, we got good news.
我们得到了数据，一条来自 Twitter 的消息
We got data back,
a message back from Twitter
在270，完成，它回来了。
at 270, complete and it came back.
好的，简化的幻灯片在这里，回来作为一个美丽的小字符串在这里，嗨。
Okay, simplified slide here, came back
as a beautiful little string here, Hi.
完成后，这就是回来的东西。
On completion, that's what came back.
她以一个对象的形式回来，因为他说包装成一个对象的形式，但是
And she comes back in an object for
he says package into an object form but
我们可以得到数据所在的属性。
we can get the property
on which that data is.
就是这样，这是一个很棒的 tweet。
And there it is,
is the high string with a great tweet.
跟着这个人，嗯？
Follow this person, hmm?
所以在完成的时候，我们得到了这个可爱的回答，但是
So on completion,
we've got this lovely response, but
它卡在浏览器里了。
it's stuck in the web browser.
怎么做？
How?
托德，它是怎么回到 JavaScript 中的呢？
How, Todd,
does it get back into JavaScript?
在 JavaScript 的全局内存中它会被分配到什么地方？
What is it gonna be assigned to back
in global memory in JavaScript?
演讲者2: 未来数据值。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: Future data value.
Will Sentance: Future data value property spot on.
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Future
data value property spot on.
就这样，他会触发什么运行，托德？
And at that,
he's gonna trigger what to run, Todd?
讲者2: 未完成的功能。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: The unfulfilled functions.
威尔 · 森特斯: 是的，没有完成的功能，说得好。
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Yeah,
the unfulfilled functions, well put.
哪一个是特别的，这里是我们的？
Which is specifically, here is our?
讲者二: 展示 显示功能,
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: Display.
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Display function,
输入了什么？
with what as its input?
讲者2: 价值。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: The value.
Will Sentance: 太棒了，值属性就是值，字符串？
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Fantastic, the value
property which is the value, the string?
讲者二: 你好 威尔 · 森坦斯: 嗨。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: Hi.
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Hi.
托德说的非常好，非常非常好。
Excellent from Todd, very very nice.
所以我们在这里，大大延迟了270毫秒。
So here we are,
way later at 270 milliseconds.
270毫秒,
270 milliseconds,
我们会打电话给你，你可能已经打过去了，等等，真的吗？
we are going to call, and
you may already be going, hold on, really?
什么？
What?
我们把它放到调用堆栈上。
We'll just put it on the call stack.
我们要调用的输入显示
We're gonna call display with the input of
嗨，找到了。
hi, there it is.
我的一些颜色开始变得。
Some of my colors starting to become.
显示与喜的输入，全新的。
Display with the input of hi,
and brand new.
所有人？
Everybody?
演讲者3: 执行情境。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 3: Execution context.
威尔 · 森特斯: 是的，没错。
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Yeah, exactly.
我们开始了吗，我们把父母放在最后了吗？
Did we initiated,
did we put the parenths on the end?
不，这些会自动启动
No, these will auto stuck on for
仍然是一个全新的执行环境。
us by JavaScript,
still a brand new execution context.
所以我们进入它，然后它是本地的。
So and into it we go and then it's local.
威尔 · 森特斯: 记忆就是输入的数据，托德,
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Memory is what's
the data that goes in, Todd,
就是再次提醒我们。
is just remind us again.
价值是多少? 演讲者2: 高。
The value is?
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: High.
威尔 · 森特斯: 高，但是里面显示，它的标签是什么？
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: High, but
inside display, what's the label for it?
讲者二: 资料 威尔 · 森特斯: 数据，是的，正是如此。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: Data.
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Data, yeah, spot on.
就是这个。
There it is.
数据，然后我们控制日志数据，也就是说我们控制日志，托德？
Data, and then we console log data
which is to say we console log, Todd?
讲者二: 高 威尔 · 森塔斯: 高,
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: High.
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: High,
托德不厌其烦地说高。
Todd's not tired of saying high.
这就是，在270毫秒，人们。
There it is, and
at 270 milliseconds, people.
我们有一个控制台日志。
We have a console log.
嗨，我的天哪。
Hi, my goodness.
我的天啊。
My goodness.
[笑声]我的天啊，看看那个。
[LAUGH] My goodness, look at that.
所有的主动栏不可思议的获取功能是不可思议的,
All of that initiative bar incredible
fetch function are incredible,
不是函数。
not function.
外观函数，触发这个背景工作,
Facade function,
that triggered this background work,
触发网络请求。
trigger the network request.
去上网，把数据带回来。
Off to the Internet,
brought back the data.
它会去哪里，我们该怎么处理它？
Where is it gonna go, and
what are we gonna do with it?
不要惊慌。
Don't panic.
我们立刻在 JavaScript 中得到了一个漂亮的对象,
We got immediately in
JavaScript a beautiful object,
承诺对象，有两个属性。
the promise object, with two properties.
一个值，这是自动的
One, a value, that was automatically
更新了你好，刚说完话
updated with the Hi,
that came back from speaking
在互联网的背景下，获取工作的另一面。
to the Internet in the background,
the other side of fetches work.
当它回来的时候，我们不知道谁会回来，不要惊慌。
And when it did come back, we don't
know who's gonna come back, don't panic.
我们准备了一个可以自动运行的函数，输入是
We had a function ready to be auto run,
with the input being that
返回的 value 属性或者从 Twitter 返回的数据的值。
value property that came back or the value
of the data that came back from Twitter.
由于该函数的输入在230毫秒显示卡住了
As the input of that function at 230
milliseconds display was stuck on
凉爽的一面与高输入，我们能够控制日志 hi。
the cool side with high input and
we were able to console log hi.